我们的博客发布的一件事
One thing that our blog post
现在仍然缺少一些图像。
is still missing right now is some images.
所以现在让我们学习如何使用 HTML &lt;img&gt;元素。
And so let's now learn how to use the HTML &lt;img&gt; element.
所以，如果我们查看演示页面，
So, if we check out the demo page,
然后我们注意到这里有两个
then we notice that here we have two
种重要的图像。
kind of important images.
所以，我们这里有这张大图，
So, we have this big image here,
哪种说明了博客文章。
which kind of illustrates the blog post.
然后我们也有这张作者的照片。
And then we also have this photo here of the author.
所以现在让我们开始在这里合并这张图片
And so let's now start by incorporating this image here
进入我们的博客。
into our blog.
因此，图像当然在我们的项目文件夹中。
So, the images are, of course, in our project folder.
因此，他们附带了启动文件。
So, they came with the starter files.
我们将在这里包括的一个，
And the one that we are going to include here,
是这个帖子图片。
is this post image.
所以当你双击时你会看到，
So you see when you double click,
所以当你打开这个文件时，
so when you open this file,
那么VSCode实际上是能够显示图像文件的，
then VSCode is actually able to display image files,
并且没有任何问题。
and without any problems.
所以我们想要这个图片就在这个作者之后。
So we want this image right here after this author.
所以基本上图像是一个障碍
So basically the image serves as a barrier
文章开头之间，
between the beginning of the article,
和页面的其余部分，所以顶部。
and the rest of the page, so the top part.
现在我想这里，实际上这里的标题，
Now I think that here, actually this title here,
所以这个&lt;h2&gt;元素应该在作者之前。
so this &lt;h2&gt; element should be before the author.
让我们把它移到这里。
Let's move that down here.
对，所以首先，当然，
Right, so first, of course,
就像我们在这里一样，需要来实际的标题。
like we have it here, needs to come the actual title.
所以标题元素，只有作者，
So the heading element, and only then the author,
然后这里的图像。
and then this image here.
好的，但无论如何，让我们现在包含 &lt;img&gt;元素。
Okay, but anyway, let's now include the &lt;img&gt; element.
再说一次，就在这一段之后，
So again, right here after this paragraph,
我们想要包含这张图片。
we want to include this image.
所以就像任何其他元素一样，
So just like any other element,
我们从这样写开始。
we start by writing it like this.
但现在请记住我实际上是如何告诉你的
But now remember how I actually told you
在本节的第一讲中，
in the first lecture of this section,
&lt;img&gt; element 是一个特殊的元素，
that the &lt;img&gt; element is a special element,
那是因为它没有任何内容，
and that's because it doesn't have any content,
因此它也没有结束标签。
and therefore it also doesn't have a closing tag.
相反，我们所做的是简单地添加斜线
Instead, what we do is to simply add the slash
在元素的最后。
here at the very end of the element.
现在你可能想知道我们是否在这里没有指定任何内容
Now you might wonder if we don't specify any content here
对于这个&lt;img&gt;元素，
for this &lt;img&gt; element,
那么 HTML 如何知道它应该显示哪个元素。
then how will HTML know which element it should display.
这是一个很好的问题，
And that is an excellent question,
这给我们带来了 HTML 中的一些新东西，
which brings us to something new in HTML,
这是属性。
which are attributes.
所以属性基本上是数据片段，
So attributes are basically pieces of data,
我们可以用它来描述元素。
which we can use to describe elements.
所以HTML中有很多不同的属性，
So there are lots of different attributes in HTML,
其中之一是 &lt;source&gt;属性。
and one of them is the &lt;source&gt; attribute.
这就是我们现在感兴趣的。
And so that's the one we are interested in right now.
所以&lt;来源&gt;像这样，SRC，然后是一个相等的，
So &lt;source&gt; goes like this, SRC, and then an equal,
然后我们需要这样的双引号，
and then we need double quotes like this,
然后我们可以简单地指定图像的名称。
and then we can simply specify the name of the image.
所以请记住，那是 post-img.jpg。
So remember, that is post-img.jpg.
所以我们只写post-img，
And so we just write post-img,
我们甚至可以让 VSCode 自动完成
and we could even allow VSCode to auto complete
我们的代码，比如点击这里，
that code for us, like by clicking here,
或下降，实际上这没有用。
or going down, and actually that didn't work.
但是如果我们只是在这里输入，
But if we just hit enter here,
那么这样就可以了。
then that would work just fine.
所以再次，我们可以手动编写它，
So again, we can write it manually,
或者只是使用 VSCode 的自动完成功能。
or just use VSCode's auto complete functionality.
实际上就是这样，
And that's actually it,
那是v我们需要的任何基础知识
that's the very basics that we need
为了显示图像。
in order to display an image.
所以如果我们现在重新加载它，
So if we reload this now,
你会看到它确实在这里。
you will see that indeed here it is.
太好了，所以再一次，让我们快速回顾一下。
Great, so again, let's just quickly recap.
我们没有指定图片
We did not specify the image
在这个元素中使用一些内容。
using some content in this element.
相反，我们需要做的是指定一个属性。
Instead, what we needed to do was to specify an attribute.
在这种情况下，它是 &lt;source&gt;属性。
And in this case, it's the &lt;source&gt; attribute.
记住一个属性
And remember that an attribute
基本上就像一个数据，
is basically like a piece of data,
所以一条描述这个元素的信息。
so a piece of information describing this element.
所以这里我们描述源
So here we are describing the source
浏览器基本上应该从中读取图像。
from which the browser should basically read the image.
好的。
All right.
现在，除了&lt;source&gt;属性，
Now, besides the &lt;source&gt; attribute,
我们可以为图像指定其他属性，
there are other attributes that we can specify for images,
我们不应该跳过的一个是 alt 属性。
and one that we should never skip is the alt attribute.
所以我们这样写，
So we write it like this,
alt 代表替代文本。
and alt stands for alternative text.
所以基本上我们需要在这里指定
So basically what we need to specify here
是一些应该描述图像内容的文本。
is some text that should describe what the image is about.
出于各种原因，这非常重要。
And this is very important for various reasons.
其中之一是它将允许搜索引擎，
One of them is that it will allow search engines,
比如谷歌浏览器，
such as Google Chrome,
真正了解图像中的内容，
to actually know what is in the image,
因为没有这个描述，
because without this description,
搜索引擎真的不知道知道
search engines don't really have a know of knowing
图像实际上是关于什么的。
what the image is actually about.
其次，也许更重要的是，
And second, and probably even more important,
是通过指定图像的描述，
is that by specifying the description of the image,
我们也可以让盲人使用网站。
we can also allow blind people to use a website.
所以使用屏幕阅读器的用户
So users who use a screen reader
不会看到图像，
will not see the image,
但他们将拥有屏幕阅读器
but instead they will have the screen reader
阅读替代文本，以便对他们进行描述。
read the alternative text, so the description to them.
所以永远不要跳过这个属性。
So never skip this attribute.
总是写一个好的描述是非常重要的。
It's very important to always write a good description.
所以在这里，假设这里的这张图片是HTML代码
So here, let's say that this image here is HTML code
在屏幕上。
on a screen.
好的，现在这在视觉上不会改变
Okay, now this will not visually change
实际上我们在这里看到的。
actually what we see here.
所以让我们重新加载，除非图像出于某种原因
So let's reload, unless the image for some reason
找不到。
can not be found.
例如，假设我们在这里忘记了 G。
So let's say that we forgot the G here, for example.
所以现在这个图像路径是完全错误的。
And so now this image path is completely wrong.
所以如果我们现在重新加载，
So if we now reload,
那么浏览器将无法找到图像，
then the browser will not be able to find the image,
但相反，它将做什么
but instead, what it will do
然后在这里打印我们的描述。
is to then print our description here.
这就是我们在此处提供的屏幕上的 HTML 代码。
So that's the HTML code on a screen that we gave it here.
好的，这实际上是替代文本的另一个用例。
Okay, so that is actually another use case of the alt text.
让我们把它放回去，我们实际上还没有完成。
Let's put it back, and we are actually still not done.
所以我们可以在这里指定更多的属性，
So we can specify some more attributes here,
在这种情况下，这非常重要。
which are quite important in this case.
所以我的意思是
So the ones that I mean
是图像宽度和图像高度。
are the image width and the image height.
所以现在这张图片有点太大了。
So right now this image here is a little bit too big.
所以让我们将其宽度指定为 500 像素，
And so let's specify its width to 500 pixels,
不用担心这 500 像素是什么意思，
and don't worry yet about what these 500 pixels mean,
或者确切地说是一个像素。
or exactly what a pixel is.
一旦我们到达 CSS 部分，我们将更多地讨论这一点，
We will talk more about that once we reach the CSS section,
但现在让我们只写宽度，并将其设置为 500，
but for now let's just write width, and set it to 500,
然后让我们看看，好吧。
and then let's see, okay.
所以现在它把图像缩放到 500 的宽度，
So now it's scaled the image to a width of 500,
它还自动保持纵横比
and it automatically also maintained the aspect ratio
的图像。
of the image.
好的，但我们也可以指定。
All right, but we can also specify that.
所以除了宽度，我们还可以指定高度，
So besides the width, we can also specify the height,
应该是200。
which should be 200.
我知道这一点，因为我知道图像尺寸。
And I know that because I know the image dimensions.
所以如果我们再次打开它，
So if we open this up again,
你在这里看到原始图像是一千乘四百。
you see here that the original image is a thousand by 400.
因此，如果我将宽度指定为 500，
And so if I specify the width as 500,
这只是一千的一半，
which is just half of a thousand,
那么这里的高度也必须是400的一半，
then the height must also be half of 400 here,
所以那将是200。
so that would be 200.
好的，现在看起来应该一样了。
Okay, so that should now look the same.
确实如此，但当然，如果我想要的话，
And it does, but of course, if I want it,
例如，我可以把它做成一个正方形，
I could make it a square, for example,
然后会完全扭曲图像，
which would then completely distort the image,
就像我们在这里看到的那样。
just as we see here.
当然我们不想要那个，所以把它放回去，我们开始吧。
Of course we don't want that, so put it back and here we go.
太好了，这就是我们包含图像的方式
Great, so this is how we include images
成 HTML 文档。
into an HTML document.
而这里的这个只是我们想要的第一个。
And to this one here was only the first one that we wanted.
另一张图片是这个作者图片
The other image is this author image
就在此作者段落的上方就在这里。
right here above this author paragraph right here.
所以我们现在想要的形象就是这个，劳拉·琼斯，
So the image that we want now is this one, Laura Jones,
我们希望它的高度和宽度为 50 像素。
and we want it with a height and a width of 50 pixels.
好的，所以我有另一个挑战给你。
Okay, so I have another challenge for you.
这次我想让你做什么
And what I want you to do this time
是包括我刚才给你看的这张图片
is to include this image that I just showed you
在这个地方你自己。
on your own right here in this place.
好的，花点时间，暂停视频，
Okay, so take a minute, and pause the video,
并包含这个 50 x 50 像素的图像。
and include this image with 50 by 50 pixels.
然后我会在一分钟内回到这里并提供解决方案。
And then I'll be back here in a minute with the solution.
好吧，所以希望你能在那里多练习。
All right, so hopefully you got some more practice there.
所以形象，我将立即开始
So image, and I will immediately start
写属性，最后我会，
writing the attributes, and I will then in the end,
关闭元素。
close the element.
所以在这里我们想要劳拉琼斯，
So here we want Laura Jones,
现在我只需按 Enter 或 Return
and now I will just hit enter or return
在此处自动完成文件名。
to auto complete the file name here.
然后是替代文字，
And then the alt text,
假设这是劳拉·琼斯的头像，
let's say that this is a Headshot of Laura Jones,
不是乔纳斯，而是一个高度，又是这里，
and not Jonas, and a height, and here again,
我们现在可以按 Enter 或返回以自动完成此操作。
we could now hit enter or return to auto complete this.
但我实际上希望你写这些属性
But I actually want you to write these attributes
自己动手，让它们进入你的脑海。
by yourself by hand, so that they get into your head.
所以这真的很重要。
So that's really important.
所以高度和宽度为 50，仅此而已。
So a height and a width of 50, and that's it.
所以让我们关闭元素，保存它，
So let's close the element, give it a save,
然后 Prettier 做得很好
and then Prettier does this nice job
将这些属性中的每一个放在一行中，
of putting each of these attributes here in one line,
这使它很容易看到。
which makes it really easy to see.
其实让我们关闭我们的侧边栏，让我们看看。
Actually let's close down our sidebar here, and let's see.
现在我们开始。
And here we go.
所以这是劳拉琼斯现在的照片。
So here is that picture of Laura Jones now.
不错，不错，进步很大。
Okay, well done, nice progress.
所以现在我们知道图像是如何工作的，
So now we know how images work,
以及属性如何工作。
and how attributes work as well.
实际上我们可以指定属性
And actually we can specify attributes
也适用于 HTML 中的其他一些元素。
also on some other elements in HTML.
这是一个非常重要的地方
And one where this is very important
实际上是 HTML 元素本身。
is actually the HTML element itself.
所以在这个 HTML 元素中，
So here in this HTML element,
我们应该指定我们用于此网页的语言。
we should specify the language that we use for this webpage.
所以对于这个文件，我们可以通过说空白来做到这一点，
So for this document, and we can do that by saying blank,
所以指定 lang 属性，
so specifying the lang attribute,
然后在这种情况下，因为它是英语，
and then in this case, since it is English,
我们可以将其设置为 EN，
we can set it to EN,
但对于其他语言，还有其他代码。
but for other languages, there are other codes.
例如，对于德语，可能只是 DE，
For example, for German, just probably DE,
或者对于葡萄牙语，它将是 PT。
or for Portuguese, it would be PT.
如果你有任何其他语言，
And if you have any other language,
您可以通过谷歌搜索轻松找到代码。
you can just easily find out the code by Googling.
我们可以而且实际上应该做的另一件事，
Another thing that we can, and actually should do,
其中需要属性是指定字符集
which needs attributes is to specify the character set
在文档中使用。
that is used in the document.
所以这是进入头脑的东西，
So that is something that goes into the head,
因为它是一条信息
because it is a piece of information
描述文档。
that describes the document.
所以这里我们需要另一个新元素。
So here we need another new element.
这被简单地称为meta，代表元数据。
And this is simply called meta, which stands for metadata.
所以元数据意味着关于数据的数据。
So metadata means data about the data.
所以在这里我们描述的是字符集，
And so here we are describing that the character set,
我们用这个属性来描述。
which we describe by this attribute.
所以我们说所说的字符应该是UTF-8，
So we say that the character said should be UTF-8,
这基本上是我们使用的所有简单字符
which basically is all the simple characters that we use
在英语中。
in the English language.
现在这里的这个是这些元素中的另一个
Now this one here is another of these elements
没有结束标签，
that doesn't have a closing tag,
所以我们就这样关闭它。
and so we just close it like this.
好的？
Okay?
现在我不会花很多时间
Now I'm not spending a whole lot of time
关于这些元素，关于这类东西，
on these elements, and on this kind of stuff,
因为后来当你真正建立自己的页面时，
because later when you actually built your own pages,
那么这一切都会自动发生。
then this will all happen automatically.
好的？
Okay?
所以这只是为了向你展示
So this was just to show you that
这只是另一种方式或另一个地方
this is just another way or another place
我们需要一些属性，
in which we need some attributes,
然后我们需要为它指定一个值。
where we then need to specify a value for it.
好的？
All right?
所以这里的UTF-8就是我们指定的值
00:12:32,780 --> 00:12:34,83​​3
对于这个字符集属性。
So UTF-8 here is the value that we specified
for this character set attribute.
好的，是的，我想这就是本次讲座的内容了。
Okay, and yeah, I think that's it for this lecture.
那么，我们下期再见。
So, see you in the next one.